<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Gerrit on 临水轩志</title>
    <link>https://yumminhuang.github.io/categories/gerrit/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Gerrit on 临水轩志</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <copyright>2018 ~ Yaming Huang</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 03 Dec 2016 14:21:57 +0800</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://yumminhuang.github.io/categories/gerrit/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Build Gerrit Plugins</title>
      <link>https://yumminhuang.github.io/note/buildgerritplugin/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 03 Dec 2016 14:21:57 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yumminhuang.github.io/note/buildgerritplugin/</guid>
      <description>Gerrit plugins can be built with both Buck and Maven.
NOTE: Developing Gerrit plugins requires installing JDK first.
Build by Maven If plugin contains pom.xml file, it can be built with Maven.
 Install Maven, see Maven Doc about Installing Apache Maven Check out plugin source code  git clone https://gerrit.googlesource.com/plugins/reviewers  Build with Maven  mvn clean package Maven will automatically download all dependencies and build source code. You will be able to find jar file in $WORKSPACE/target directory.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Customize Gerrit Homepage</title>
      <link>https://yumminhuang.github.io/note/gerrithomepage/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 03 Dec 2016 14:20:37 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yumminhuang.github.io/note/gerrithomepage/</guid>
      <description>Customized Homepage To customize Gerrit homepage, we added the following files:
 $site_path/etc/GerritSiteHeader.html HTML is inserted below the menu bar, but above any page content. This is a good location for an organizational logo. $site_path/etc/GerritSiteFooter.html HTML is inserted at the bottom of the page, below all other content. Display links to FAQ, user guides, etc. $site_path/etc/GerritSite.css The customized CSS rules are inlined into the top of the HTML page. $site_path/static/logo.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Find Gerrit Outdated Projects</title>
      <link>https://yumminhuang.github.io/note/findgerritoutdatedprojects/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 03 Dec 2016 14:09:23 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yumminhuang.github.io/note/findgerritoutdatedprojects/</guid>
      <description>Recently, I had a job to clean up our Gerrit server. First of all, I have to find projects which we can deprecate and remove them.
Here is the solution how I found outdated Gerrit Projects.
Gerrit Administrator can use gerrit gsql command to access Gerrit backend database and query outdated projects. The below SQL can find projects whose lastest changes were updated 180 days ago.
 The results could be the candidates of deprecating projects.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>